<resources>
    <string name="app_name">WHEELS</string>
    <string name="complete_co">COMPLETE CONTROL</string>
    <string name="jedi_like_p">Jedi like powers at your finger tips.</string>
    <string name="guides">GUIDES</string>
    <string name="we_got">We got your back, ask us anything car related\n and we will have it sorted.</string>
    <string name="assistance">ROAD SIDE ASSISTANCE</string>
    <string name="get_support">Get support when you need it most.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">A number of major, overarching privacy regulations have been made law in the last few years, and they’re
        not restricted to single nations. One of these regulations covers 28 countries, some apply to two or three countries, and one was
        developed by one state (California) but manages to apply to the entire USA.The most significant regulation is the EU’s
        (European Union’s) General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), which came into effect in May of 2018 and quite rigorously secures
        the confidentiality of the personal information of all those in the 28 EU countries. It’s 88 pages long and goes further than any
        other regulation to establish a safe online environment for consumers.Australia’s Privacy Act of 1988 was drafted before
        information technology was a major threat to personal privacy. However, its principles still apply today and the letter of the law
        has been updated to reflect current conditions.</string>
    <string name="desc">Glad you joined Wheels!
        Add your vehicle to unlock its full potential!</string>
    <string name="faq_head">POPULAR TOPICS</string>


    <string-array name="questions">
        <item>Remote Start With Vehicle Controls</item>
        <item>Remote Unlock with Wheels App</item>
        <item>Road Side Assistance</item>
        <item>Remove Vehicle</item>
        <item>Change Units Of Measurement</item>
        <item>My Profile Details</item>
        <item>Vehicle Overview</item>
        <item>Terms and conditions</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="answers">
        <item>Select this on vehicle page</item>
        <item>There are two images on vehicle page which can be used for remote lock/unlock vehicle</item>
        <item>Click on the triagular button on the top of vehicle image on Vehicle page.\nIt will alllow you to call our road side assistance team.</item>
        <item>Go to the Accounts page.\nThen select the Settings icon.\nUser can see a remove vehicle option which  can be used</item>
        <item>Go to the Accounts page.\nThen select the Settings icon.\nUser can see a Units of Measurement option to toggle between the units.</item>
        <item>Go to the Accounts page.\nThen select the Edit Profile icon.\n</item>
        <item>Navigate to the Vehicle page.\nUser will be provided with Tirepressure details,fuel level,oil life,odometer reading and distance to empty.</item>
        <item>Go to the Accounts page.\nThen select the Settings icon.\nUser can click on Terms and Privacy to go through details.</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->

</resources>
